I did a full set up for a new project with AI and it took me like a lot of
hours to get everything planned after planning and did this, did this.
And I said, yeah, I'm not happy.
I want to do this, this, and this before we proceed to the next step.
So after I think three or four hours, we were done planning
and that's a lot of time.
So the first thing I did, I asked it to write down a full prompt to
explain AI next time, how I want to do the planning exactly in this style.
So now my second project, I just put in the MD file.
I say, read this.
This is how I want to do the planning.
Okay.
Do we start?
And then it just starts interviewing me.
What do we need?
Well, how do we do this?
And what does this set up?
What server are we using?
Et cetera.